[Music]
All right, here is a little thing we
have been cooking on with the Contoso
demo tool. I'm in a company here with no
analytic analytics demo data. And if I
open Conto
demo tool, you will notice that there is
a new kit on the block analytics. So
this is adding some new documents if you
need to demo reporting or PowerBI.
Okay. So without this installed I can uh
just search for quotes
sales quotes and you can see I have two
quotes. Now let me show you what happens
if you're in a company where you have
enabled or where you have ran the
analytics part of the demo tool. So let
me switch over to that.
So this is a company called all demo
data. So if I go here and search for
sales quotes
you will notice that we now have a lot
more quotes like 18. So uh so this is
what that module does. It's it adds new
document types and you can watch the
Business Central launch edition video to
learn more in a couple of weeks. This
should land in Business Central in
27.1ish.
Thanks for watching. Have a good day.